<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Dmitriy Shilin</title>
    <link>https://dshil.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Dmitriy Shilin</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 15:13:34 +0300</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dshil.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Git: tuning performance on Windows</title>
      <link>https://dshil.github.io/blog/git_tunning_performance_windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Dec 2018 15:13:34 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dshil.github.io/blog/git_tunning_performance_windows/</guid>
      <description>Preface An internet was designed in a such way that almost nobody remembers the days when there is no internet. People just got used to this phenomenon, like an air, in the same way, there are some people who remember those days and we should protect them as the UNESCO area. This feeling that the internet has been at all times shows that it was very well-designed and later - implemented.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git: better commit message</title>
      <link>https://dshil.github.io/blog/git_better_commit_message/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Dec 2018 07:37:30 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dshil.github.io/blog/git_better_commit_message/</guid>
      <description>I always do git log and explore what changes were made by other developers. It is my habit and I don&amp;rsquo;t expect that other developers do the same. But I would totally be very happy if a git history will become more clean and understandable not only in big open-source projects but also in a majority of company in the software development industry. You need to follow some rules to keep your git history healthy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>MacOS: missed clock guide</title>
      <link>https://dshil.github.io/blog/macos_missed_clock_guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2017 08:03:19 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dshil.github.io/blog/macos_missed_clock_guide/</guid>
      <description>Table of contents
 Preface Motivation High resolution time management in Linux Mach Kernel Mach Clock API Deprecated Mach Clock API Links  Preface This is a story of a little fight with an obscure OS X clock API.
When it comes to high-resolution time management in OS X wouldn&amp;rsquo;t it be a dreamy to have the following routines:
 Receive current monotonically incrementing time value. Sleep for a specified interval.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
